<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Single Card App Maxine</string>
    <string name="Maxine">I\'m Maxine Nwaneri Founder of \"THE FUTURE IS GREATER\"</string>
    <string name="Future">The Future is Greater is a Success Coaching and Training Practice with the vision of helping ambitious women create and experience exactly that, A Greater Future in terms of reaching their potential, and making a greater impact in the world through their work, while living stress free personal lives they love.</string>
    <string name="Vision">This vision for a greater future has always been a deep part of who our founder Maxine Nwaneri is. Born in Nigeria where it is custom for parents to give their children names with meanings they hope will reflect the child\'s reality, her parents named her \"Nkiruka\" in addition to Maxine, which literally translates to \"The Future is Greater\".</string>
    <string name="Believe">She believes this has led her to develop an optimistic, aspirational and continuous learning approach to life, which has helped her overcome significant obstacles and challenges in her own life, and shaped the strategies she impacts hundreds with today both through her practice, and contributions in the Huffington Post.</string>
    <string name="Prior">Prior to setting up her Coaching Practice, Maxine went from what she describes as \"a complete mess and failure\", to graduating at the top of her class, studying with some of the most intelligent minds in the world while obtaining her MBA from the Prestigious University of Cambridge, and acquiring over a decade\'s experience working in large corporations internationally in Senior Management and Leadership Positions.</string>
    <string name="Citizen">Maxine is truly global citizen, having lived in several countries on 4 Continents, travelled to numerous others, and worked successfully with teams and clients around the globe. She is passionate about creating a fantastic family life with her husband and daughter, spending good times with loved ones, travel, fashion, learning, personal development, assisting those in need, and empowering her Clients to uncover and live out their best lives.</string>
    <string name="Focus">Her unwavering focus remains to continue to create an even greater future for herself, her family, and her clients around the world. We\'d love for you to join us!</string>
    <string name="Adress">Bergen Norway</string>
    <string name="Phone">+00112233445566</string>
    <string name="Email">maxine@maxinenwaneri.com</string>
</resources>
